<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>George Pacheco:~</title>
    <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on George Pacheco:~</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://g-pacheco.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Warsaw, Poland</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/warsaw-poland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/warsaw-poland/</guid>
      <description>Palace of Culture and Science (Polish: Pałac Kultury i Nauki), is a notable high-rise building in central Warsaw, Poland. With a total height of 237 metres (778 ft) it is the tallest building in Poland, the 5th-tallest building in the European Union (including spire) and one of the tallest on the European continent. Constructed in 1955, it houses various public and cultural institutions such as cinemas, theatres, libraries, sports clubs, university faculties and authorities of the Polish Academy of Sciences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hel, Poland</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/hel-poland-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/hel-poland-3/</guid>
      <description>Hel Peninsula (Polish: Mierzeja Helska) is a 35-km-long sand bar peninsula in northern Poland separating the Bay of Puck from the open Baltic Sea. The width of the peninsula varies from approximately 300 m near Jurata, through 100 m in the most narrow part to over 3 km at the tip. Since the peninsula was formed entirely of sand, it is frequently turned into an island by winter storms. Until the 17th century the peninsula was a chain of islands that formed a strip of land only during the summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hel, Poland</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/hel-poland-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/hel-poland-2/</guid>
      <description>Hel Peninsula (Polish: Mierzeja Helska) is a 35-km-long sand bar peninsula in northern Poland separating the Bay of Puck from the open Baltic Sea. The width of the peninsula varies from approximately 300 m near Jurata, through 100 m in the most narrow part to over 3 km at the tip. Since the peninsula was formed entirely of sand, it is frequently turned into an island by winter storms. Until the 17th century the peninsula was a chain of islands that formed a strip of land only during the summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arizona, US</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/arizona-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/arizona-us/</guid>
      <description>The Grand Canyon is a steep-sided canyon carved by the Colorado River in Arizona, United States. The canyon is 277 miles (446 km) long, up to 18 miles (29 km) wide and attains a depth of over a mile (6,093 feet or 1,857 meters).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago, US</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/chicago-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/chicago-us/</guid>
      <description>Chicago, officially the City of Chicago, is the most populous city in the U.S. state of Illinois, and the third-most-populous city in the United States. With an estimated population of 2,705,994 (2018), it is also the most populous city in the Midwestern United States. Chicago is the county seat of Cook County, the second-most-populous county in the US, with a small portion of the northwest side of the city extending into DuPage County near O&amp;rsquo;Hare Airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panaji, India</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/panaji-india-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/photos/panaji-india-2/</guid>
      <description>Panaji, formerly Panjim, is the capital of the Indian state of Goa and the headquarters of North Goa district. It lies on the banks of the Mandovi River estuary in the Ilhas de Goa sub-district (taluka). With a population of 114,759 in the metropolitan area, Panjim is Goa&amp;rsquo;s largest urban agglomeration, ahead of Margão and Vasco da Gama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/bio/</guid>
      <description> I am an Evolutionary Biologist currently doing a post-doc at the Technical University of Denmark being advised by Dr. Jakob Hemmer Hansen &amp;amp; Dr. Dorte Bekkevold. We are part of the Population Genetics section located at the small town of Silkeborg in Jutland. This section is part of DTU Aqua, a well-known institute in the field of aquatic resources.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Please find below an abridged version of my CV. You can download a full PDF version from here. George Pacheco
Evolutionary Biologist
DTU Aqua / Vejlsøvej 39, 8600 Silkeborg • Denmark
ganpa@aqua.dtu.dk
+45 4088-8017
Initially trained in Biology in the Brazilian Northeast, I have worked on several projects in the vein of animal evolutionary genomics investigating a diverse range of taxa—from tiny Collembolans to culturally evolving killer whales, which has given me a vast experience in the molecular lab and a fair understanding of the rationale behind bioinformatic analyses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myReads/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/myreads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/myreads/</guid>
      <description>I read quite a few Science Communication books throughout my bachelor times in Natal. Undoubtedly, titles such as The Drunkard&#39;s Walk and Lonely Planets greatly contributed to my initial scientic education. Although I still very much harbour a desire to read on various scientific subjects (I really like Physics, for instance), at some point one must focus on a specific field considering the short half-life of a human begin, and thus my reading of this kind of genre is no longer as diverse as it once was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description>17 August 2021/ I participated in the virtual MarGen II meeting since our in-person meeting was postponed to October — looking forward to finally meeting everyone personally when the right time comes!16 August 2021/ Waldir&#39;s article has now been submitted to Genes.31 July 2021/ I officially launched this webpage — welcome everyone! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Please find below an abridged version of a list with plublication. You can download a detailed PDF version from here. 2021/   Conservation Genomics of the Endangered Seychelles Magpie Robin (Copsychus sechellarum): A Unique Insight into the History of a Precious Endemic Bird.
Cavill et al. IBIS. / Accepted
  The Germline Mutational Process in Rhesus Macaque and Its Implications for Phylogenetic Dating.
Bergeron et al. GigaScience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>So far in my scientific carrer I have mainly worked on projects in the vein of Animal Evolutionary Genomics. To some of these I chiefly collaborated with wetlab work, while to others my contribution was on the drylab front, and yet to other projects I wore both the wetlab and the drylab hats (that was certainly the case for those projected I led). You will find below a selected list of the projects I have participated alongside with a short explaination on how I contributed to each of them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
