<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>George Pacheco:~</title>
    <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on George Pacheco:~</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://g-pacheco.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bio/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/bio/</guid>
      <description> I am an Evolutionary Biologist currently doing a post-doc at the Technical University of Denmark being advised by Dr. Jakob Hemmer Hansen &amp;amp; Dr. Dorte Bekkevold. We are part of the Population Genetics section located at the small town of Silkeborg in Jutland. This section is part of DTU Aqua, a well-known institute in the field of aquatic resources.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Please find below an abridged version of my CV. You can download a full PDF version from here. George Pacheco
Evolutionary Biologist
DTU Aqua / Vejlsøvej 39, 8600 Silkeborg • Denmark
ganpa@aqua.dtu.dk
+45 4088-8017
Initially trained in Biology in the Brazilian Northeast, I have worked on several projects in the vein of animal evolutionary genomics investigating a diverse range of taxa—from tiny Collembolans to culturally evolving killer whales, which has given me a vast experience in the molecular lab and a fair understanding of the rationale behind bioinformatic analyses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myReads/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/myreads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/myreads/</guid>
      <description>I read quite a few Science Communication books throughout my bachelor times in Natal. Undoubtedly, titles such as The Drunkard&#39;s Walk and Lonely Planets greatly contributed to my initial scientic education. Although I still very much harbour a desire to read on various scientific subjects (I really like Physics, for instance), at some point one must focus on a specific field considering the short half-life of a human begin, and thus my reading of this kind of genre is no longer as diverse as it once was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description>17 August 2021/ I participated in the virtual MarGen II meeting since our in-person meeting was postponed to October — looking forward to finally meeting everyone personally when the right time comes!16 August 2021/ Waldir&#39;s article has now been submitted to submitted to Genes.31 July 2021/ I officially launched this webpage — welcome everyone! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Please find below an abridged version of a list with plublication. You can download a detailed PDF version from here. 2021/   Conservation Genomics of the Endangered Seychelles Magpie Robin (Copsychus sechellarum): A Unique Insight into the History of a Precious Endemic Bird.
Cavill et al. IBIS. / Accepted
  The Germline Mutational Process in Rhesus Macaque and Its Implications for Phylogenetic Dating.
Bergeron et al. GigaScience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research/</title>
      <link>https://g-pacheco.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-pacheco.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>10K Bird Project/ webpage. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
